DEBUG: GeminiClient initialized with OpenRouter using model: google/gemini-2.0-flash-001
Testing Interview Evaluation...
Interview Result: {'score': 30, 'summary': "The candidate provides very brief and superficial answers. They lack depth, detail, and quantifiable achievements. Their 'Tell me about yourself' response is too basic and doesn't highlight their key skills or motivations for the role. The conflict resolution answer is generic and provides no specific examples or a structured approach.", 'strengths': [], 'improvements': ['Provide more detailed and insightful answers.', 'Quantify achievements with metrics and examples.', 'Demonstrate a structured approach to problem-solving, especially conflict resolution.', 'Tailor responses to the specific job role and company.'], 'feedback': ['"Tell me about yourself" should include more about your background, relevant projects, and career aspirations. Briefly mention what excites you about software engineering and aligns with the job requirements.', 'For the conflict resolution question, provide a specific example using the STAR method (Situation, Task, Action, Result). Outline the specific steps you took to resolve the conflict.', 'Answers are too short and lack depth. Elaborate on your skills and experiences.', "Don't just say you 'try to understand the root cause'; describe *how* you do that by asking clarifying questions, actively listening, and demonstrating empathy.", 'The answers lack specific technical details. Be prepared to discuss your experience with React and Python in more detail (e.g., specific frameworks, libraries, or projects).']}

Testing Test Evaluation...
Test Result: {'score': 100.0, 'feedback': 'The user answered all questions correctly. Excellent performance!', 'detailed_analysis': [{'question_id': 1, 'status': 'Correct', 'feedback': 'Correct! Binary search has a time complexity of O(log n).'}]}
